

MYO MI MI SHARR

• DETAILS •

Singapore +6593714939 myomimisharr@gmail.com

> Date of birth 11 Aug 1991

Nationality Myanmar

LINKS

LinkedIn Profile

Portfolio Website

• SKILLS •

WordPress

PHP

HTML

CSS

Jquery

JavaScript

Bootstrap

SEO

React JS

MySQL

Adobe Photoshop

Figma

Git

SharePoint

Note JS

• LANGUAGES •

English

Myanmar

PROFILE

I'm Sharr, a seasoned web developer with over a decade of experience in fast-paced environments. I hold a Bachelor of Engineering degree in Information Technology from Mandalay Technological University. My expertise includes PHP, WordPress, HTML, CSS, jQuery, JavaScript, Bootstrap, React.js, Photoshop, Figma, MySQL, Git, SEO, SFMC, Formsite, and SharePoint. I focus on creating user-friendly websites that meet client needs efficiently and effectively.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering, Technological University, Mandalay

2011 - 2012

Graduated with high honors.

Bachelor of Technology, Technological University, Mandalay

2007 - 2011

Graduated with high honors.

Certificate of Completion WSQ Search Engine Optimisation (SEO) Training Course, Equinet Academy, Singapore

October 2022

Successfully completed Search Engine Optimization Course.

From Superpowers to Great Teams, IDEO UIDEO, Singapore

October 2023

Has completed the course requirements.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Web Developer at Ace Pointer Information Technology, Singapore

December 2021 — Present

- Planning website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with PHP, Wordpress, HTML, CSS, Jquery, JavaScript, React.js, API and other editing software.
- Overseeing back-end development using PHP to maintain website integrity, security and efficiency.
- Providing effective troubleshooting and remediation for web applications.
- Implementing Google-based SEO and ad campaigns to meet budget specifications.

Web Developer at Agility Logistics, Singapore

December 2019 — November 2021

- Successfully identified, diagnosed, and fixed website problems, including broken links, typographical errors, and formatting issues.
- Provided ongoing efficiency and security maintenance and patched on website interface to maintain viability after launch.
- Collaborated with Digital Marketing Team, representing web team to establish project goals, projections and milestones.

Web Developer at Nexlabs Myanmar, Yangon

June 2017 — May 2019

- Focused PHP and HTML development outside of WordPress for landing pages, micro-sites, etc
- Coordinated with team of UX designers to create new Web Content Management system
- Maintained an organized workflow using a project management tool (like GitHub)

CMS Developer at Revo Tech Myanmar, Yangon

July 2015 — May 2017

Web Developer & Web Designer at Myanmars.NET, Yangon

October 2013 — March 2015

★ MOST SUCCESSFUL TECHNOLOGICAL ACHIEVEMENT

Capitol Singapore, Restaurants & Cafes

Project Link

Chijmes, Food & Entertainment

Project Link

Agility, Asia Pacific Logistics

Project Link

Agility, All Insights

Project Link

Chindwin PSB, Private College

<u>Project Link</u>

Golden Hill Tower, Room Rental

Project Link

▼ REFERENCES

• References available upon request